<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.4.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2025-12-09T22:31:12-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Teejys Diary</title><entry><title type="html">Welcome</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/welcome.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome" /><published>2025-12-09T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2025-12-09T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/welcome</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/welcome.html"><![CDATA[<p>Dear Diary,
 I realized that I have so much goin on in my mind… and I forgot that I was a (terrible) writer hehe.
Plus, I have been wondering how I can bridge my communities.. It’s weird having separate audiences in Youtube, Tiktok, or Instagram.</p>

<p>I was thinking about doing a mailing list, which I still may do for some reason (idk. entrepreneurs recommend it, so I’ll try it! I think it’s smart in the sense that any or all of my accounts could get banned, and I would lose all touch w the homies in an instant…)</p>

<p>But yeah, what better way to ramble my nonsense, and incoherently witness myself in the form of written word than to add a blog to my website, a project which… exists! :D</p>

<p>like, whoaa. I have a website, haha.</p>

<p>That’s so cool. I should be utilizing this more! There is so much more potential than I know.</p>

<p>Annyywayyzz, so yeah.</p>

<p>WELCOME to the blog!</p>

<p>See you in the next post besties.</p>

<p>(don’t  talk to me don’t look at me don’t smell at me don’t you even think about it!)</p>

<p>nah, you can talk to me tho.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dear Diary, I realized that I have so much goin on in my mind… and I forgot that I was a (terrible) writer hehe. Plus, I have been wondering how I can bridge my communities.. It’s weird having separate audiences in Youtube, Tiktok, or Instagram.]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Tunnel</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/the-tunnel.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Tunnel" /><published>2025-12-09T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2025-12-09T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/the-tunnel</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2025/12/09/the-tunnel.html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>December 9th, 2025</strong>
<em>song-philosophy, creative-process, worldbuilding, community, gratitude, artistic-vision</em></p>

<p>![Cool new fan](/assets/images/cool%20new%20fan.png)</p>

<p>On the notion of my <a href="https://youtube.com/shorts/Pc62VHsKtDo">most recent original acoustic song video</a>…</p>

<p>Would you guys like me to tell u when i wrote these songs in the video’s descriptions?</p>

<p>I think that information is a fun, but I try to leave stuffz like that out as to not muddy any waters.</p>

<p>Any time I perform, I want to do my best to honor the song as much as I can, however feels right to me emotionally in that moment.</p>

<p>It’s cool too, cuz any time i play one of my songs for u guys, chances are, it’ll be slightly different than any other time i’ve played it. In my opinion, even the smallest difference creates a completely new experience for us to enjoy. That can be a simple note change, to the way I soften or harden my voice. This too is another reason why I enjoy the jazz mindset so much!***</p>

<p>.
.</p>

<p>I feel like for u guyz, adding extra details could muddy the perception of hearing a song for the first time. I’m down to give fun facts about my headspace when writing these songs, or any other details you may be interested in, if yous want!</p>

<p>I think I have at least 1 abstract detail/connection for each song.</p>

<p>Anyways, please do ask any clarifying questions about my art, mindset or philosophies whenever they pop up!</p>

<p>I usually try to let the art speak for itself, but as a psychology and philosophy oriented person, I understand that interpretations of any artistic works can benefit from the insights of the author.</p>

<p>So, let me know if ur curious!</p>

<p>I have lots i wanna say, tho i really am in no rush to let it all out at once! Doing slow drips keeps things fresh anyways, and it gives a chance for any passerbyers to join in on the experience too without feeling like they need to do a lot of catch up work.</p>

<p>(Tho i try to structure the delivery of my art where it invites the curious to dig deeper if they want. It’s partially why I enjoy the concept of “feeding into my abyss” so much. Since the beginning, i have always favored depth over instant delivery. Those who are curious have a long breadcrumb trail to follow, and i try not to spoil the rewards by dumping it all in one place.)</p>

<p>.
.
.
.</p>

<p>I’m sure one of these days, after i pop off and become a global sensation, i’ll get a really astute interviewer who can help me appreciate this heaping pile of  (sh)art in a way we can all enjoy, anywayz.</p>

<p>I’m just happy to be riding in the first place… and I am so thankful for everyone who is strolling along! Or should i say, uhhh scrolling! A heh.. tehe…</p>

<p>anyways, i’m sure that is all obvious to anyone who has been around for more than 20 minutes of consuming my work..</p>

<p>I truly love what I do. I feel so honored to be given this opportunity to build this little universe here for us all to appreciate. My parents have helped me so much, it’s unbelievable. And I am so grateful to be here every day.</p>

<p>And i am so grateful for all of you dudes too! To my long time homies/supporters, my new friends that hop in the comments every so often, and I am so grateful for my lurkers too!</p>

<p>It’s insane how many of y’all have stuck around with me all these years… i’m still comprehending it all.. and it feels like my heart grows every time i think about you guys.</p>

<p>Your presence means so much, and I am sure i would have given up pursuing creativity as a vocation had i been alone this time.. i am so sure.</p>

<p>You guys give me strength every day, and i appreciate the gentle reminders of warmth and presence you all send as i pour my heart out in the form of these breadcrumbs across the internet.</p>

<p>I see the future already, and we.. myself and y’all, the Teejsters…. are going to shape history..</p>

<p>And we will serve as anchors for the cultures of the world for generations to come, as far as my little asian blind eyes can see..</p>

<p>I hope you are all ready.</p>

<p>Tho I am sure our independent lives will have an endless amount of new pits and tunnels to drive thru….</p>

<p>I have no doubt in my mind that in this tunnel right now.. in my little echo chamber of niche obscurity and absurd mental health awareness (or unawareness heh, if u were here last year you would get it.)</p>

<p>That faint glimmer in the distance will be within arms reach before any of us know it!</p>

<p>The tunnel will wish us farewell soon enough.</p>

<p>And then we can meet the world anew.. and it will wrap us in an unfamiliar warmth as we immerse ourselves in the glory this newfound light.</p>

<p>.
.</p>

<p>Ok byeee!</p>

<p>:)</p>

<p>Thx for reading, truly.</p>

<p>Care.</p>

<p>Tj out.</p>

<p>![[cool new fan.png]]</p>

<p>I have always seen my songs as standards (like Jazz Standards, where they have a loose form and anyone can integrate their own personalities in its expession!). So, you already know I have an endless amount of content coming our way :D</p>

<p>So again, please feel free 2 request any of my songs any time, and I’ll get to it sooner than later!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"><![CDATA[December 9th, 2025 song-philosophy, creative-process, worldbuilding, community, gratitude, artistic-vision]]></summary></entry></feed>